<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<quotes>
    <quote>Success is not final, failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts. - Winston Churchill</quote>
    <quote>Believe you can and you're halfway there. - Theodore Roosevelt</quote>
    <quote>Don't watch the clock; do what it does. Keep going. - Sam Levenson</quote>
    <quote>The only way to do great work is to love what you do. - Steve Jobs</quote>
    <quote>It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop. - Confucius</quote>
    <quote>Everything you've ever wanted is on the other side of fear. - George Addair</quote>
    <quote>Hardships often prepare ordinary people for an extraordinary destiny. - C.S. Lewis</quote>
    <quote>It always seems impossible until it is done. - Nelson Mandela</quote>
    <quote>Don't be pushed around by the fears in your mind. Be led by the dreams in your heart. - Roy T. Bennett</quote>
    <quote>Life is what happens when you're busy making other plans. - John Lennon</quote>
    <quote>You are never too old to set another goal or to dream a new dream. - C.S. Lewis</quote>
    <quote>What you get by achieving your goals is not as important as what you become by achieving your goals. - Zig Ziglar</quote>
    <quote>It's not the load that breaks you down, it's the way you carry it. - Lou Holtz</quote>
    <quote>The only limit to our realization of tomorrow will be our doubts of today. - Franklin D. Roosevelt</quote>
    <quote>Do not wait to strike till the iron is hot, but make it hot by striking. - William Butler Yeats</quote>
    <quote>Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it. - Charles R. Swindoll</quote>
    <quote>The best way to predict the future is to create it. - Peter Drucker</quote>
    <quote>Failure will never overtake me if my determination to succeed is strong enough. - Og Mandino</quote>
    <quote>Act as if what you do makes a difference. It does. - William James</quote>
    <quote>Don't count the days, make the days count. - Muhammad Ali</quote>
    <quote>Set your goals high, and don't stop till you get there. - Bo Jackson</quote>
    <quote>If you're going through hell, keep going. - Winston Churchill</quote>
    <quote>Success is not the key to happiness. Happiness is the key to success. If you love what you are doing, you will be successful. - Albert Schweitzer</quote>
    <quote>The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. - Eleanor Roosevelt</quote>
    <quote>Success is not in what you have, but who you are. - Bo Bennett</quote>
    <quote>Challenges are what make life interesting and overcoming them is what makes life meaningful. - Joshua J. Marine</quote>
    <quote>When you have a dream, you've got to grab it and never let go. - Carol Burnett</quote>
    <quote>It's not whether you get knocked down, it's whether you get up. - Vince Lombardi</quote>
    <quote>Opportunities don't happen, you create them. - Chris Grosser</quote>
    <quote>"If you want to achieve greatness stop asking for permission." --Anonymous</quote>
    <quote>Believe in yourself and all that you are. Know that there is something inside you that is greater than any obstacle. - Christian D. Larson</quote>
    <quote>Your passion must come from the heart, not the head. - Katerina Stoykova Klemer</quote>
    <quote>Focus on being productive, not busy. - Tim Ferriss</quote>
    <quote>You may encounter many defeats but you must not be defeated. In fact, it may be necessary to encounter the defeats, so you can know who you are, what you can rise from, how you can still come out of it. - Maya Angelou</quote>
    <quote>Though no one can go back and make a brand new start, anyone can start from now and make a brand new ending. - Carl Bard</quote>
    <quote>Wake up determined. Go to bed satisfied. - Unknown</quote>
    <quote>Believe in yourself, take on your challenges, dig deep within yourself to conquer fears. Never let anyone bring you down. You got to keep going. - Chantal Sutherland</quote>
    <quote>Limitations live only in our minds. But if we use our imaginations, our possibilities become limitless. - Jamie Paolinetti</quote>
    <quote>Your attitude, not your aptitude, will determine your altitude. - Zig Ziglar</quote>
    <quote>Work until your idols become your rivals. - Drake</quote>
    <quote>Believe you can and you’re halfway there. - Theodore Roosevelt</quote>
    <quote>If opportunity doesn’t knock, build a door. - Milton Berle</quote>
    <quote>Wake up with determination. Go to bed with satisfaction. - Unknown</quote>
    <quote>You're braver than you believe and stronger than you seem, and smarter than you think. - A.A. Milne</quote>
    <quote>Happiness is not something readymade. It comes from your own actions. - Dalai Lama</quote>
    <quote>Fortune sides with him who dares. - Virgil</quote>
    <quote>Go confidently in the direction of your dreams. Live the life you have imagined. - Henry David Thoreau</quote>
    <quote>You have to fight through some bad days to earn the best days of your life. - Unknown</quote>
    <quote>Don’t limit your challenges. Challenge your limits. - Unknown</quote>
    <quote>Hardships often prepare ordinary people for an extraordinary destiny. - C.S. Lewis</quote>
    <quote>If you want to lift yourself up, lift up someone else. - Booker T. Washington</quote>
    <quote>Strive for progress, not perfection. - Unknown</quote>
    <quote>Only I can change my life. No one can do it for me. - Carol Burnett</quote>
    <quote>Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue that counts. - Winston Churchill</quote>
    <quote>Either you run the day or the day runs you. - Jim Rohn</quote>
    <quote>All progress takes place outside your comfort zone. - Michael John Bobak</quote>
    <quote>Don’t watch the clock; do what it does. Keep going. - Sam Levenson</quote>
    <quote>Things may come to those who wait, but only the things left by those who hustle. - Abraham Lincoln</quote>
    <quote>Never give up on what you really want to do. The person with big dreams is more powerful than one with all the facts. - Albert Einstein</quote>
    <quote>Things work out best for those who make the best of how things work out. -John Wooden</quote>
    <quote>If you are not willing to risk the usual you will have to settle for the ordinary. -Jim Rohn</quote>
    <quote>Take up one idea. Make that one idea your life--think of it, dream of it, live on that idea. Let the
        brain, muscles, nerves, every part of your body, be full of that idea, and just leave every other idea
        alone. This is the way to success. --Swami Vivekananda</quote>

</quotes>



